# **Dean Warman**

25 Fakes Road Hemsby NR29 4JL 07784 677848

dean-warman88@hotmail.co.uk

With a hard working and motivated personality you will find me to me a key member within your team. I have experience of working in very busy environments and enjoy working with people. With an enthusiastic attitude and a need to keep busy I'd be a great addition to any hard working team.

### **Strengths and Skills:**

- \* Factory Work experience and aware of Health & Safety in the workplace
- \* Can complete difficult tasks to the highest standard
- \* Works well as part of a team or individually to hit targets
- \* I can perform multiple tasks efficiently and can work well under pressure

### **Employment History**

January 3 2023 March 26 2023

**Teaching Assistant** 

**Cliff Park** 

Main Responsibilities are: Preparing the classroom for lessons and tidying it up afterwards, assisting with lesson plans, supporting children across the curriculum, providing extra assistance to children with special needs, motivating and encouraging students and looking after children who are unwell or upset.

#### August 13 2019 – February 10 2022

**Retail Assistant** 

Tesco

While at Tesco my main job roles were to assist on the front end of there store, although during my time I have worked in nearly every department from checkouts to warehouse, at points I have taken on supervisor roles in order to cover breaks and absence meaning I have excellent flexibility and drive to learn.

#### **April 2015 - November 1 2018**

**Ride Operator** 

**Pleasurewood Hills** 

At Pleasurewood Hills my main jobs were; to make sure my ride is safe to use and to clean the general area around my ride, I must engage customers and make sure they are having fun and deal with any complaints they might have.

## January 2015 - March 2015

Retail Assistant (Voluntary)

**British Heart Foundation** 

Whilst at the British Heart Foundation, I test any electrical donations to ensure they are working correctly. I also work in the warehouse and front of house as and when needed.

### 28 July 2014 - December 2014

Kitchen Staff (Voluntary)

**Food Bank** 

Working on a volunteering basis, I assist the Food Bank with serving food to the homeless. This is a very rewarding position and I enjoy spending time with others volunteering.

### October 2013

**Factory Worker** 

**Bernard Matthews** 

Working on a busy factory line, I worked with raw meat and ensured all Health & Safety procedures were being followed. My shift pattern was varied and I also worked nights.

### July 2013 - August 2013

Retail Assistant (Voluntary)

**British Heart Foundation** 

Volunteering on an as and when basis, I helped the front of house staff with till work and answered any customer queries. I also looked through stock ensuring all donated items were able to be reused and tagged with appropriate prices.

### **Education:**

2014 – 2019 SIA License

2009 – 2011 Denes High School Educated to a GCSE Level References are available on request